Every Al has something to protect.
Am I doing this right?
I don’t think I’m doing this right.
Al Chun.
Can you hand me that paint cup?
Thank you.
Well, I can tell you this...
Alan Hyggen.
I’m not gonna spend my retirement on land.
Alex Palacios.
I’m a lot.
Oops! Sorry.
Let's give it up for...
Mr. Al and Allie Singh.
Als who start a business.
She’s the boss now, she’s taking over.
And Als who keep it running.
These are good to go.
Perfect.
Quiet Als.
Go... Go...
Yes!
Loud Als.
C'MON! TOUCHDOWN!
Competitive Als.
It's actually Ali.
They’ve all got something to protect,
whether it’s these Als,
or just one perfect little...
Jeff.
Whoever you are,
you’ve got something to protect.
I have all the time in the world
to do something I love.
And with investment, retirement
and insurance know-how...
Here, look at the camera.
Prudential can help protect
your life's work.
There you are.